Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: The Unbearables, 14224
  - Poetry Game, 1996, 14246 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Reading #3, undated; 14245 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Gender Bender Reading, 1996, 14244 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Borders--Atticus, Computer-linked reading. 1996, 14243 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Mnemonic City Reading, 1995, 14242 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Unbearables Assembling Magazine #4, undated; 14241 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Unbearables Assembling Magazine #5, undated; 14240 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Unbearables Portfolio #2, 1996, 14239 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Unbearables Portfolio #3, undated; 14238 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photo of Carter, Rapaport, C.X. Hunter and Watson, 261013 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Unbearables Corpse. Anarchist Picnic, undated; 14237 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Voices Of Aftershock -- 1990, 14236 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Unbearables Money, undated; 14235 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Unbearables Anthology Reviews, undated; 14234 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Response To Beat Protest Criticism, undated; 14233 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Unbearables Anthology Artwork, File #1, undated; 14232 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Unbearables Anthology Artwork File #2, undated; 14231 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Unbearables Anthology materials, undated; 14230 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Basinski Review, undated; 14229 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cups Interview by Janice Eidus, undated; 14228 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rollo Whitehead's Health and Whereabouts, undated; 14227 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Subject Files, 14017
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists, 14076
    This subseries contains materials about writers and artists, and includes reviews, clippings, and other miscellaneous printed materials.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the artist's last name.
    - Ackerman(s), undated; 14223 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Adams, Jeff, undated; 14222 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, Vicky, undated; 14221 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Roberta, undated; 14220 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Anthony, Bill, undated; 14219 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Armijo, Richard, undated; 14218 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Basquiat, Jean-Michel, undated; 14217 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Bauman, Jane, 263528 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Benderson, Bruce, undated; 14216 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bennett, Will, undated; 14215 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bevel, Mat, undated; 14214 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Blachy, Jimbo, undated; 14213 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Blagg, Max, undated; 14212 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Blowdryer, Jennifer (Waters), undated; 14211 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bogosian, Eric, undated; 14210 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Borkhuis, Charles, undated; 14209 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Breuer, Lee, undated; 14208 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Brown, Ken, undated; 14207 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Brown, Ken, File 2, undated; 14206 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Bukowski, Charles, undated; 14205 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Burns, Charles, undated; 14204 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Cale, David, undated; 14203 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Cannon, Steve, undated; 14202 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Cardin, Jorga, undated; 14201 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Carter, Michael, undated; 14199 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Cherches, Peter, undated; 14198 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Chung, Nhi (Nancy), undated; 14197 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Coe, Sue, undated; 14196 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Cohen, Nancy a.k.a. Nancy Koan, undated; 14195 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Colby, Todd, undated; 14194 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Cole, David, undated; 14193 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Coleman, Joe, undated; 14192 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Crumb, Robert, undated; 14191 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Cullman, Brian, undated; 14190 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Daitch, Susan, undated; 14189 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Dali, Salvador, undated; 14188 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Deitch, Kim, undated; 14187 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Desnoyers, Dana, undated; 14186 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Dickson, Jane, undated; 14185 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Drooker, Eric, undated; 14184 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Duhamel, Denise, undated; 14183 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Eberhardt, Isabelle, undated; 14182 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Eidus, Janice, undated; 14181 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Feast, Jim, undated; 14180 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Fishberg, Lawrence, undated; 14179 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Fitzpatrick, Tony, undated; 14178 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Freeman, Dan, undated; 14177 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated; 14176 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated; 14175 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Giorno, John, undated; 14174 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Golden, Mike, undated; 14173 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Gordon, Mel, undated; 14172 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Gray, Spalding, undated; 14171 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Gunderson, Joanna, undated; 14170 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Hamill, Janet, undated; 14169 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Haring, Keith, undated; 14168 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Head, Glenn, undated; 14167 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated; 14166 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Huberman, David, undated; 14165 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Hunter, Christian, undated; 14164 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Indiana, Gary, undated; 14163 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Isaac, Jeffrey a.k.a. Zagreus Bowery, undated; 14162 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - James, Darius, undated; 14161 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Jankowski, Matty, undated; 14160 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Joyce, W, undated; 14159 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Kasper, Michael, undated; 14158 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated; 14157 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Kaz, undated; 14156 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack, undated; 14155 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - King, J.D., undated; 14154 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 14153 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 14152 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 14151 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 14150 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 14149 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Kolm, Ron ("In a word"), undated; 14148 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated; 14147 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 14146 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Kruger, Barbara, undated; 14145 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kruth, John, undated; 14144 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 14143 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - LaBombarda, Michael, undated; 14142 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Litzsky, Tsaurah, undated; 14141 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Lopatin, Judy, undated; 14140 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - McCall, Bruce, undated; 14139 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - McGlyn, Bob, undated; 14138 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, undated; 14137 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - McGrath, Patrick, undated; 14135 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Madore, Michael, undated; 14134 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Mandl, Dave, undated; 14133 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Mathews, Harry, undated; 14132 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Maynard, Joe, undated; 14131 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Mazzucchelli, D, undated; 14130 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated; 14129 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Miller, Stephen Paul, undated; 14128 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Moisan, Jim, undated; 14127 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Moriarty, J, undated; 14126 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Myles, Eileen, undated; 14125 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Olsen, Lance, undated; 14124 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Ostashevsky, Eugene, 261016 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Otterness, Tom, undated; 14123 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Padua, Jose, undated; 14122 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Panter, G, undated; 14121 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Passaro, Vince, undated; 14120 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Pincus, Harry, undated; 14119 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 14118 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Potash, Chris, undated; 14117 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Randall, Michael, undated; 14116 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Rankin, Susan, undated; 14115 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Rattray, David, undated; 14114 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Rosen, Jonathan, undated; 14113 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Rower, Ann, undated; 14112 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated; 14111 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Sandlin, David, undated; 14110 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Savage, Tom, undated; 14109 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Sedaris, David, undated; 14108 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Sendak, Maurice, undated; 14107 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Shalom (full, legal name: Shalom Newman), undated; 14106 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated; 14105 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated; 14104 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sipes, Steven, undated; 14103 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 14102 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sparrow (legal name: Michael Gorelick), undated; 14101 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sparrow, undated; 14100 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated; 14099 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Strausbaugh, John, undated; 14097 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Texier, Catherine, undated; 14096 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Tillman, Lynne, undated; 14095 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated; 14094 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Topp, Mike, undated; 14093 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ulin, David, undated; 14092 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Vitale, Alfred, undated; 14091 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Walker, John, undated; 14090 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Watson, Carl, undated; 14089 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Watson, John, undated; 14088 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Weiss, Thomas, undated; 14087 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated; 14086 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Wilson, Blair, undated; 14085 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, Peter Lamborn (aka Hakim Bey), undated; 14084 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Witz, Bob, undated; 14083 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Wodizcko, Krysztof, undated; 14082 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 14081 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated; 14079 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Yourgrau, Barry, undated; 14078 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Zummer, Thomas, undated; 14077 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects, 14018
    This subseries contains materials about subjects in the downtown scene, like stamp art, vend art, etc. It also contains items documenting Ron Kolm's career working for independent bookstores.
    - Berserker Magazine, undated; 14075 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Between C & D Anthology, undated; 14074 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Between C & D Magazine, undated; 14073 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Bookstores, undated; 14072 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Book Zine Web Fair, Cafe Nico, 1996, 14071 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Business Cards, undated; 14070 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Cartoon, exhibitions, undated; 14069 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Cartoonists, undated; 14068 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - City Lights, Booksellers & Publishers, undated; 14067 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - East Village Culture, undated; 14066 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Fact Sheet Five Magazine, undated; 14065 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Fiction Collective 2, undated; 14064 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Films, undated; 14063 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Fusion Arts Books, undated; 14062 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Graffiti, undated; 14061 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Hallwalls, undated; 14060 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Handelines, undated; 14059 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Hard Press Poetry Postcards, undated; 14058 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Hoboken Terminal Magazine, undated; 14057 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Instant Classics, undated; 14056 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Katonah -- Zummer materials, undated; 14055 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Limited Time Only Magazine, undated; 14054 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Local Boy Makes Good--Appearances #21, Mike Topp Issue, undated; 14053 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Low Tech Press, undated; 14052 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Madame Rosa's, undated; 14051 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Magazines, undated; 14050 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous Art File, undated; 14049 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Mondo Barbie, undated; 14047 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Music, undated; 14046 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - National Poetry Magazine Of The Lower East Side, undated; 14045 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Neoism -- Correspondence Art, undated; 14044 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - New Leaves Review, undated; 14043 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New Morning Bookstore, undated; 14042 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Panic Button Press, undated; 14041 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Pinched Nerves, undated; 14040 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Poetry Project, undated; 14039 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Poet's House, 261058 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Portable Lower East Side, undated; 14038 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Public Illuminations Magazine, undated; 14037 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Rant Magazine, undated; 14036 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - RAW, undated; 14035 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Reviews - Subyear Files, 261059 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Rubber Stamps, undated; 14034 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop, undated; 14033 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop -- Letter File, undated; 14032 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Seven Deadly Sins, undated; 14031 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Single Cell Show--Katonah Art Museum/Gallery, undated; 14030 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Smoke Signals, undated; 14029 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Soho Arts Weekly (SAW), undated; 14028 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Southpaw Magazine, undated; 14027 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Technoscience & Cyberculture--Peter Lamborn Wilson, undated; 14026 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Test Drive (Appearances #22), undated; 14025 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Vend Art, undated; 14024 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Ward Nasse Gallery, undated; 14023 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Wexner & Katonah, undated; 14022 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - WFMU 91.1 Radio Station, undated; 14021 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Writer's Market, undated; 14020 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Zone Magazine, undated; 14019 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Series V: Photographs, 13988
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables, 261021
    This subseries consists of one small box of photographs, mostly of The Unbearables.
    - Whole Heart by Shalom (Shelved in oversize), undated; 14016 (Binder A)
    - Sparrow For President photo, undated; 14015 (Binder A)
    - Photo of Denise Duhamel, undated; 14014 (Binder A)
    - Merry Christmas photo of Richard Peabody, undated; 14013 (Binder A)
    - 3 photos from the "Low Tech Manual" reading, 1981 Participant: Ron Kolm, 14012 (Binder A)
    - Photo of "Assissi" with the name "Jeffrey Isaac" on back, undated; 14011 (Binder A)
    - Photo of Thomas Zummer & Leslie Thornton filming "The Great Invisible", undated; 14010 (Binder A)
    - Production still of "The Great Invisible" with Thomas Zummer and others, undated; 14009 (Binder A)
    - Photo of "Isabelle Eberhardt and her mother, Natalie de Moerder" from "The Great Invisible", undated; 14008 (Binder A)
    - 20 color photos of "Unbearables" at Shandon Star 9/25/96. Participants: Ron Kolm, Joe Maynard, Bob McGlyn, Susan Scutti, Bonnie Finberg, Liz Resko, Bart Plantenga, Mike Golden, Dave Mandl, Michael Randall, Hal Sirowitz, Tsaurah Litzky, Lorraine Schein, 1996; 14007 (Binder A)
    - 2 Photos of Joe Lewis, undated; 14006 (Binder A)
    - Photo of unidentified woman, undated; 14005 (Binder A)
    - Two sheets of old, photo booth pictures taken at Bleecker St. Bar, 1990? Participants: Ron Kolm, Jose Padua, Ralph Ackerman, Mike Golden, Carol Wierzbicki, 14004 (Binder A)
    - A Large, black & white photo of Unbearables for the Village Voice (oversized). Participants: Bob Witz (standing) Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Michael Carter, Alfred Vitale, Jim Feast (seated), undated; 14003 (Binder A)
    - B Small, black & white photo of Unbearables for the Village Voice. Participants: Bob Witz, Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Alfred Vitale, Jim Feast, Michael Carter, undated; 14002 (Binder A)
    - Photos --33 photos from the Memory City Reading. Participants: Ron Kolm, Carl Watson, Jim Feast, Bob Witz, Hal Sirowitz, Carol Wierbicki, Bart Plantenga, Alfred Vitale, Michael Carter, Jill Rapaport, Rob Hardin, Joe Maynard, David Huberman, Christian X. Hunter, Bonnie Finberg, undated; 14001 (Binder A)
    - Photos -- 28 photos from a Rant Benefit Reading. Participants: Jim Feast, Alfred Vitale, Susan Scutti, Ron Kolm, Tsaurah Litzsky, Joe Maynard, Dave Mandl, Bart Plantenga, Michael Carter, Carol Wierzbicki, and others, undated; 14000 (Binder A)
    - Large photo of the Saint Mark's Bookshop at it's old location (oversized), undated; 13999 (Binder A)
    - 2 color photos of paintings by Michael Randall, undated; 13994 (Binder A)
    - 2 Photos of Bob Witz with his paintings, undated; 13996 (Binder A)
    - 1 small "Kodalux" box of slides. Contents: 6 slides by William Anthony illustrating Ron Kolm's work, undated; 13997 (Binder A)
    - 1 sheet of slides "Voices of Aftershock", undated; 13998 (Binder A)
    - Miscellaneous photos of "Unbearables", undated; 13995 (Binder A)
    - 1 black & white photo of Michael Randall painting, 1 slide. (Both in envelope with the words: "Michael Randall painting that became cover for Kolm's Plastic Fact."), undated; 13993 (Binder A)
    - 21 Photos from Second New Yorker Protest. Participants: Ron Kolm, Alfred Vitale, Tom Savage,Jim Feast, Bart Plantenga, Joe Maynard, Sparrow, Carol Wierzbicki, Bob Witz, Jill Rapaport, Michael Carter, Lorraine Schein, Shalom, Michael Carter, Lawrence Fishberg, Lorraine Schein, William Anthony, & others, undated; 13992 (Binder A)
    - 5 Photos from a Reading on the Brooklyn Bridge. Participants: Peter Lamborn Wilson, Tom Savage, Dave Mandl, Jim Feast, Bart Plantenga, Bruce Weber, David Huberman, Sparrow, Ron Kolm, Alfred Vitale, and others, undated; 13991 (Binder A)
    - Photo of a painting by Patrick Stevenson, undated; 13990 (Binder A)
    - 19 photos of Unbearables at Armstrong's Bar for Cups Magazine May 31, 1996. Participants: Ron Kolm, Sharon Mesmer, Jim Feast, Marvin Taylor, Janice Eidus, Mike Topp, Alexander Lawrence, 13989 (Binder A)
  - Subseries B: Coliseum Books Photographs, 261022
    This subseries consists of one binder of pictures from throughout Ron Kolm's tenure at Coliseum Books.
    - Coliseum Bookstore Christmas Party, 1990s; 261023 (Binder B)
    - Darwin Hageman and John Underwood, 261024 (Binder B)
    - Pam Carter, 2001; 261025 (Binder B)
    - Corey Groom, 2001; 261026 (Binder B)
    - Michael Audas and Ronald Stephenson, 2001; 261027 (Binder B)
    - Lino Azevedo, 2001; 261028 (Binder B)
    - Annie, 261035 (Binder B)
    - Weber Jenson, 261029 (Binder B)
    - Kevin and Jefferson, 261030 (Binder B)
    - Staff at McCoy's, 2000; 261031 (Binder B)
    - Store Christmas Party, 2000, 261032 (Binder B)
    - Lino as Elvis/Closing Party, 2002; 261033 (Binder B)
    - Area Excavated for Store Elevator, 1994; 261034 (Binder B)
- Series VI: Announcements, 13847
  This series contains nnouncements for readings, gallery shows, and other events.
  - Subseries A: Readings, 13921
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by venue.
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 13987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Alchemical Theater, undated; 13986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Anseo, undated; 13985 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Attitude Art, undated; 13984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Back Fence, undated; 13983 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Bernard & Steve's, undated; 13982 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Biblio's, undated; 13981 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Blue Mountain, undated; 13980 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - B.O.B, undated; 13979 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Bookstore Readings, undated; 13978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Brecht Forum, undated; 13977 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - CBGB, undated; 13976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Cedar Tavern, undated; 13975 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Chez Rollo, undated; 13974 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Cold Fish, undated; 13973 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Darinka, undated; 13972 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - DIA Center For The Arts, undated; 13971 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Dixon Place, undated; 13970 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Ear Inn, undated; 13969 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Exit Art, undated; 13968 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Fez Under Time Cafe, undated; 13967 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - The Garden (6th St.& Ave. B), undated; 13966 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - The Gas Station, undated; 13965 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Granary Books, undated; 13964 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Hearn Gallery, undated; 13963 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Image Theater, undated; 13962 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - The Kitchen, undated; 13961 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - The Knitting Factory, undated; 13960 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - La Mama Galleria, undated; 13959 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Life Cafe, undated; 13958 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Limelight, undated; 13957 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - The Living Theater, undated; 13956 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Medicine Show, undated; 13955 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Neither/Nor, undated; 13954 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - New York Public Library, undated; 13953 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Cafe Nico, undated; 13952 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Cafe No Bar, undated; 13951 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Nuyorican Poets Cafe, undated; 13950 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Palsson's Restaurant, undated; 13949 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - P.S. 122, undated; 13948 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Duplicates, undated; 13947 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Poemfone, undated; 13946 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - The Poetry Project, undated; 13945 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - The Pyramid Club, undated; 13944 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Segue Foundation Performance Space, undated; 13943 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Skep, undated; 13942 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Speak Easy, undated; 13941 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Spiral Bar, undated; 13940 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - The Thread Waxing Space, undated; 13939 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Up Front Muse, undated; 13938 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Ward Nasse Gallery, undated; 13937 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Group Readings, undated; 13936 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reading Announcements, undated; 13935 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Performances (Non-Readings), undated; 13934 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Bruce Benderson, undated; 13933 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Readings-- David Rattray, undated; 13931 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Readings -- Hal Sirowitz, undated; 13930 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Readings--Barry Yourgrau, undated; 13929 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Readings -- Max Blagg, undated; 13932 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Announcements -- Plays, undated; 13928 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Book Parties/Publication Announcements, undated; 13927 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Calendars 1981--1988, 13926 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Poetry Calendars 1988-1989, 13925 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Poetry Calendars 1990, 13924 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Poetry Calendars 1991--1995, 13923 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Poetry Calendars 1996, 13922 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 13848
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by gallery or by artist.
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 13920 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Adams, Jeff, undated; 13919 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - ala Gallery, undated; 13918 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Vikki, undated; 13917 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Andrucyk, Inez, undated; 13916 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Anthony, William, undated; 13915 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Armijo, Richard, undated; 13914 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Artist's Space, undated; 13913 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Baer Gallery, undated; 13912 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Baxter, Glen, undated; 13911 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Blachy, Jimbo, undated; 13910 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bluhm, Norman, undated; 13909 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Bordo, Robert, undated; 13908 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Burkhart, Kathe, undated; 13907 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Ken, undated; 13906 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - C., Jim, undated; 13905 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Capp Gallery, undated; 13904 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - CB's 313 Gallery, undated; 13903 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Clemente, Francesco, undated; 13902 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Coe, Sue, undated; 13901 (Box 9, Folder 35)